I called you into this meeting today to discuss our performance.
今天的会议主要是讨论一下我们的业绩
As you can see our rate of growth is exceptional.
正如你所看到的   我们的增长率十分突出
Overall kids satisfaction is through the roof
孩子们总体非常满意
and our stock value has risen considerably.
我们的市值也上升很大
This is in part to your help at AGI,
这其中有你们对AGI的一份功劳
but also getting rid of that nuisance Uncle Grandpa.
还因为我们摆脱了惹人嫌的Uncle Grandpa
Now in order to perpetuate growth, we must help more kids,
现在为了增长   我们必须帮助更多的孩子
help them faster and help them cheaper.
更快 更廉价地帮助他们
Well, won't that compromise the quality of my work?
这会降低我的工作质量啊
It's not about quality, Mr. Gus, it's about profit!
重要的不是质量   盖斯先生   而是利润
I thought AGI was a nonprofit organisation.
我以为AGI是非盈利组织
Who cares about that?
谁在乎呢
Auntie, are we gonna see any of that kids' ash?
阿姨   我们能赚到更多的钱吗
Of course, Pizza Steven, if you do your part!
当然了   披萨斯蒂文   如果你做得好
In fact, if you all do your part
事实上   如果你们都做得好
aunt Grandma Industries will become an unstoppable kid-helping force
Grandma Industries 会成为帮助孩子的一股不可阻挡
that will soon rule  the entire world, hahahaha.
横扫世界的力量     哈哈哈哈哈
Well, now, who wants some ice cream?
现在谁想吃冰激凌